Bob Lazar: Area 51 and Flying Saucers is a documentary film
directed by Jeremy Kenyon Lockyer Corbell.
Area 51, flying saucers from another world - and the
program to create a fierce technology.
Bob Lazar remains the singular most famous and
controversial name in the world of UFOs.
The reason you know about Area 51 is because Lazar
came forward and told you about it.
His disclosures have turned his life upside-down and he
has tried to stay out of the spotlight.
For this reason, he has never let any filmmaker into the private
world of his daily life - that is - until now.
Corbell’s film explores Lazar’s claims through the lens of thirty years - providing rare and
never before revealed footage - guaranteed to alter the landscape of the debate.
Self - Interviewee, played by Bob Lazar.
Self - Investigative Reporter, played by George Knapp.
Self - The Narrator (voice), played by Mickey Rourke.
Self - Investigative Filmmaker, played by Jeremy Kenyon Lockyer Corbell.
Self - The Wife, played by Joy White.
Self - The Mom, played by Phyllis Tucker.
Robert Scott Lazar () is an American who, since 1989, has claimed to have been part of a classified US government project concerned with the reverse engineering of
extraterrestrial technology; he also purported to have read government briefing documents that described alien involvement in human affairs over the past 10,000 years.
A self-proclaimed physicist, Lazar supposedly worked at a secret site near the
United States Air Force facility popularly known as Area 51.
His story brought additional public attention to the facility and spawned conspiracy
theories regarding government knowledge of extraterrestrial life.
Lazar has provided no evidence of alien life or technology, and his claims about
his education and employment history are replete with fabrications.
Lazar also has been involved in criminal activity: he was convicted in 1990 for his involvement in a Nevada prostitution ring, and his
company was sentenced to probation in 2006 for violating laws prohibiting the sale of chemicals across state lines.
As well as being dismissed by skeptics, Lazar has
been denounced by some ufologists.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, government, flying saucer, alien, ufo.